Guilherme Branco Stracini

São Paulo, Brazil



linkedin.com/in/guilhermestracini



https://guilherme.stracini.com



guilherme@guilhermebranco.com.br



4 +55 11 97265-9788

Summary

Currently working in a bank, taking care of PIX project (Instant Payments), developing APIs and Open Banking integrations and functionality, direct contact with clients, regulatory agencies, other banks and technical teams to provide the best solution for both sides! Using .NET Core, SQL Server, RabbitMQ supported by DDD architecture and SOLID, DRY & KISS principles.

I am excited to contribute my strengths and proficiency in innovation toward your team efforts. As an extroverted and personable communicator with a proven track record in technical writing, my focus on building strong professional relationships has been a valuable asset throughout my career.

Well experienced with C# and JS (both, frontend and backend with NodeJS), working with financial services, e-commerce, integrations, web and desktop solutions since 2012.

I have also worked with PHP since 2007 for freelance jobs.

Check out some projects I worked on:

- Gateway integrations with MaxiPago, Adyen and PayPal.
- OnBoarding and Internet Banking projects for B2B customers (participant).
- Vitrine do Artesanato (integration).
- VTEX e-commerce PaaS (integration).
- Sankhya ERP (management, analysis, integration).
- Vitrine do Artesanato Digital digital video platform (development).
- Vitrine do Artesanato na TV digital video content portal (development).
- Canal do Artesanato subscription learning platform (development).
- Zendesk (integration).
- SAP (integration).
- Database (management).
- Some integrations libraries in C#, PHP, Rust and JS, available at https://github.com/guibranco

Experience



Senior Software Engineer

BS2 Hub

Jul 2019 - Present (1 year 1 month +)

- Implementation of PIX (Brazilian Instantly Payments BACEN)
- Development of API banking product (https://devs.bs2.com) BaaS
- Development of open banking project
- Development of APIs using .NET Core, Dapper, Entity Framework and DDD
- Deploy and development using Docker containers
- Supporting clients in integration process

🧰 Software Developer

C&A Brasil

Dec 2018 - Jun 2019 (7 months)

- Development of integrations solutions using Zendesk, SAP, Oracle and other internal systems
- Automation of payment/refund process using Adyen gateway
- Automation of process using .NET Core
- Develop new features and APIs using NodeJS (Express & HAPI)
- Develop of an unified library in .NET Core to be used internally by all teams, with commons & utils needs

Project Development Coordinator

Editora Inovacao Ltda [Inovacao Media Brazil Group]

Jan 2016 - Nov 2018 (2 years 11 months)

- Head of development of IT department. Managing dev's team, agencies and associates.
- Implement SOLID principles.
- Deploy, evangelize and speech of continuous integration and continuous delivery (CI/CD)

Software Development Analyst

Editora Inovacao Ltda [Inovacao Media Brazil Group]

Nov 2013 - Dec 2015 (2 years 2 months)

- Website development using ASP.NET C # technology and MVC standard.
- API 2 (C #) web applications for user data access (via client web application) and restricted access data management of other internal projects.
- Application development for product and order integration with the Smart Checkout / VTEX platform.
- Payment gateway integration MaxiPago for subscription management
- Management of triggers and procedures in SQL Server 2008 database.
- Disaster Management / Automated Backup Plans on SQL Server and Windows Server.
- Automated backup for Amazon Web Service S3.

IT Analyst

Editora Inovacao Ltda [Inovacao Media Brazil Group]

Nov 2012 - Oct 2013 (1 year)

- Development of video portal using C # language and MVC standard.
- Development of service integration tool (via Web Service and API) in C #.
- Monitoring and management of SQL Server database.
- Requirements gathering.
- Planning, modeling, implementation and process documentation ERP (Sankhya).

Intern - IT

Editora Inovacao Ltda [Inovacao Media Brazil Group]

Nov 2011 - Oct 2012 (1 year)

- Development of email marketing.
- Training, maintenance and installation of micro computers.
- Configuration and installation of software.
- Development of internal systems in VB.NET
- Development of complementary tools for existing projects in classic ASP and PHP.

Education



FATEC - São Caetano do Sul - Antônio Russo

Analysis and systems development, Technologist

2011 - 2013

Senac Brasil

Computer technician, Informatics

2008 - 2010

Computer technician course - 1000 hours, presencial classes.

ETEC Prof. Camargo Aranha

High School Diploma, High School/Secondary Diplomas and Certificates 2007 - 2009

Licenses & Certifications

English - CNA Ensino de Linguas

Assembly, maintenance and network - SOS Computadores

Skills

Microsoft SQL Server • C# • ASP.NET MVC • Web Services • Software Documentation • Design Patterns • Unit Testing • Continuous Integration • Requirements Gathering • Web Applications